

Wenxuan WANG Shanghai/China | +86 17621222563 wxwang.iris@gmail.com

Homepage Google Scholar

SUMMARY

I am currently a second-year Ph.D. student at Fudan University, under the supervision of Prof. Yanwei Fu and Prof. Xiangyang Xue. At present, I devote to the research of adversarial attacks, generative adversarial networks, person re-identification, face recognition, expression classification with deep learning.

EDUCATION

NORTHWESTERN POLYTECHNICAL UNIVERSITY

2013-2017

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY

FUDAN UNIVERSITY 2017-2019

M.S. IN COMPUTER APPLICATION

FUDAN UNIVERSITY 2019-Present

Ph.D. IN COMPUTER APPLICATION

PUBLICATIONS

CONFERENCE

- FMMu-Net: Face Morphological Multi-branch Network for Makeup-invariant Face Verification. **Wenxuan Wang**, Yanwei Fu, Xuelin Qian, Qi Tian, Yu-Gang Jiang, Xiangyang Xue. IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (**CVPR**), 2020.
- Long-Term Cloth-Changing Person Re-identification. Xuelin Qian, **Wenxuan Wang**, Li Zhang, Fangrui Zhu, Yanwei Fu, Tao Xiang, Yu-Gang Jiang, Xiangyang Xue. Asian Conference on Computer Vision (**ACCV**), 2020. (Oral)
- Comp-GAN: Compositional Generative Adversarial Network in Synthesizing and Recognizing Facial Expression. **Wenxuan Wang**, Qiang Sun, Yanwei Fu, Tao Chen, Chenjie Cao, Ziqi Zheng, Guoqiang Xu, Han Qiu, Yu-Gang Jiang, Xiangyang Xue. The 27th ACM International Conference on Multimedia. (**ACM MM**), 2019.
- Pose-Normalized Image Generation for Person Re-identification. Xuelin Qian, Yanwei Fu, Tao Xiang, **Wenxuan Wang**, Jie Qiu, Yang Wu, Yu-Gang Jiang, Xiangyang Xue. European Conference on Computer Vision. (**ECCV**), 2018.

PREPRINT

- A New Screening Method for COVID-19 based on Ocular Feature Recognition by Machine Learning Tools. Yanwei Fu, Feng Li, **Wenxuan Wang**, Haicheng Tang, Xuelin Qian, Mengwei Gu, Xiangyang Xue. medRxiv, 2020.
- Learning to Augment Expressions for Few-shot Fine-grained Facial Expression Recognition. **Wenxuan Wang**, Yanwei Fu, Qiang Sun, Tao Chen, Chenjie Cao, Ziqi Zheng, Guoqiang Xu, Han Qiu, Yu-Gang Jiang, Xiangyang Xue. arXiv, 2019
- A Fine-Grained Facial Expression Database for End-to-End Multi-Pose Facial Expression Recognition. **Wenxuan Wang**, Qiang Sun, Tao Chen, Chenjie Cao, Ziqi Zheng, Guoqiang Xu, Han Qiu, Yanwei Fu. arXiv, 2018

EXPERIENCE __

PING AN 2018.09-2019.06

INTERN FOR FACE FEATURE LEARNING

• Facial expression recognition under few-shot setting: This project aimed at recognizing subtle facial expression in the insufficient training data condition. I was primarily responsible for algorithm study.

TENCENT 2020.06-2021.01

INTERN FOR THE SECURITY OF DEEP LEARNING

• Adversarial attack: The project targeted to study the robustness of the deep neural networks and further generate transferable adversarial examples on both face recognition and general classification tasks.

SKILLS _

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES Experienced: Python Familiar: C | C++

PLATFORM Experienced: Pytorch | Matlab Familiar: Tensorflow | Caffe

LANGUAGES Native: Chinese Fluent: English

EXTRA

TEACHING ASSISTANT

2018.09-2019.02

• Fudan University, Information System Security.

PART-TIME TEACHER

2018.12-2019.07

• Zhangmen, teaching junior high school students Chinese.

SCHOLARSHIP

- National Scholarship, top 1%, 2016-2017
- First-class Scholarship for Excellent Master Students, Fudan University, top 10%, 2017-2018
- 'Wei Rui' Scholarship, Fudan University, top 5%, 2018-2019
- First-class Scholarship for Excellent Ph.D Students, Fudan University, top 10%, 2019-2020